AN NGUYEN

Full Stack Developer

About me

As a research scientist, I have spent the last 10 years trying to develop cures diseases afflict humans. I've always followed my passion and consequently always aim for excellence in my career.

I am now looking to apply my experience in project management, communication and critical thinking as a web developer. I readily tackle new challenges with grit and determination, as always with a smile on my face.

Contact



annguyen@sydney.edu.au



github/pleathershaman



an.theaspiringwebdeveloper.com

Education

| The Web Developer Bootcamp | 2018 - 2019 |
|----------------------------|-------------|
| Udemy | |
| | |
| The Modern React Bootcamp | 2019 - 2019 |
| Udemy | |
| Master of Science | 2011 - 2012 |
| University of Sydney | |
| | |

Experience

Molecular Imaging Scientist

2012 - 2018

ANSTO

ANSTO is Australia's primary research facility for nuclear science. In this position, managed and contributed to research projects that use nuclear imaging. I was independently running multiple projects concurrently and was the main point of contact for all correspondence and communication. I was also responsible for organising project-related administration such as contracts, budgets, regulatory compliance and non-disclosure agreements.

Research Assistant

2008 - 2011

The Save Sight Institute

My main role in this position develop new experiments to investigate the causes of a rare eye disease. In this position, I set up a pipeline for analysing the differences in protein levels in a disease model.

Skills

| HTML5 | •••• | | css | •••• |
|-------------------------|-----------|-----|------------|------|
| JavaScript | •••• | | Bootstrap | •••• |
| React | •••• | | Redux | •••• |
| Jest/Enzyme | • • • • • | | Git/Github | •••• |
| NodeJS | •••• | | MongoDB | •••• |
| Problem Solv | ing | •• | | |
| Project Management ●●●● | | | | |
| Communication | | ••• | | |

Awards

The Wenkart Foundation Grant A competitive scholarship valued at \$28,000 p.a. (AUD) awarded for Master of Science.

References

Available on request

Personal Projects

Kitchen Catalogue

Kitchen Catalogue is an online database that allows users to create, edit and organise their cooking recipes. It features a full-stack MERN application with connection to a RESTful API, email confirmation and password reset. Technologies used include, React, Redux, NodeJS, Express, MongoDB, HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript ES6+.

Link: http://kitchencatalogue.theaspiringwebdeveloper.com

Code: https://github.com/PleatherShaman/KitchenCatalogue

React Color Picker

React Color Picker is a single-page react application that helps users design their own color palettes and view different shades of a particular color. This application was the cap-stone projects of the Udemy Modern React Bootcamp. Technologies used include, React, HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript ES6+.

Link: https://reactcolorpicker.herokuapp.com/

Code: https://github.com/PleatherShaman/reactColorPicker

Inspiration Montage

Inspiration Montage is a small react application that shows users a photo gallery based in their search terms. Featuring an infinite scroll and connection to the Unsplashed API, this program provides the user with visual inspiration on nearly every topic. Technologies used include, React, HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript ES6+.

Link: https://inspirationmontage.herokuapp.com/

Code: https://github.com/PleatherShaman/InspirationMontage